{"data":[{"question":"She's quite nice but I wouldn't like to be married ________ her.","a":"with","b":"on","c":"about","d":"to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be married to sbd\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"We are always proud ________ our country.","a":"of","b":"on","c":"about","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be proud of sbd\/sth: feeling pleased about something that you have done or something that you own, or about someone or something you are involved with or related to.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"I felt sorry ________ the children when they went ________ holiday. It rained every day and they had to spend most of the time indoor.","a":"for \/ on","b":"about \/ on","c":"about \/ in","d":"for \/ in","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be\/feel sorry for somebody: to feel pity or sympathy for someone because something bad has happened to them or because they are in a bad situation.\u00a0\n- Go on: to leave the place where you are, in order to do something (go on a trip\/tour\/cruise etc).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"It wasn't polite ________ him to leave without saying a word.","a":"with","b":"to","c":"on","d":"of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- It is polite (of somebody) to do something: behaving or speaking in a way that is correct for the social situation you are in, and showing that you are careful to consider other people's needs and feelings.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"We were staying at the ........... our parents","a":"same with","b":"same as","c":"same like","d":"same about","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You can say that one thing is the same as another. Do not use like or with.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"You like chocolate, ________.","a":"and I do either","b":"and me too","c":"and I too","d":"and so do I","answer":"4","explain":"+SO is used to show agreement with positive statements. \n+SO + Auxiliary + Subject (pronoun).\u00a0\n+The Auxiliary needs to agree with the verb tense in the original statement.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"________ a doctor, I must advise you to give up smoking.","a":"As","b":"To","c":"Like","d":"Else","answer":"1","explain":"\n- As: used to say what job, duty, use, or appearance someone or something has.\u00a0\n- Like: Use like in comparisons followed by a noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Please find a bill for 50 for the advice ________.","a":"gave you","b":"what I gave you","c":"which gave you","d":"I gave you","answer":"4","explain":"\n- What\/where\/ which... can be use as a relative pronoun. Relative pronouns introduce relative clauses, which are a type of dependent clause.\u00a0\n- Relative pronouns used as an object in a restrictive relative clause: the relative pronoun may be omitted in the object position.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"She said ________ she meant him much.","a":"though","b":"like","c":"like as if","d":"as if","answer":"4","explain":"\n- As if: Use as if followed by a clause to compare a real situation with an imaginary situation.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"You play tennis ________ I do.","a":"better than","b":"more good than","c":"more well","d":"more well than","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of short adverb (well)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}